bluetooth.org 2002-12-04

# Bluetooth SIG - Privacy Policy

  |  |   | 

---|---  
  | 

* * *  
  
  | 

     \- [ Membership](http://www.bluetooth.org/sig-membership/)  
     \- [ Interest](http://www.bluetooth.org/interest_registration/)  
     \- [ Next UnPlugFest](http://www.bluetooth.org/index.htm#UPF)  
  
  | 

* * *  
  
  | 

  | 

* * *  
  
  | 

    **Contact**  
         **Bluetooth**  

> **
> 
> Bluetooth SIG, Inc. Privacy Policy
> 
> **
> 
> Bluetooth SIG, Inc. is committed to user privacy in our products and services. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices. If you give us contact information, we will treat it according to this policy.
> 
> This policy covers the Bluetooth SIG, Inc. member web site.
> 
> Bluetooth SIG, Inc. encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all web sites you visit. Please note that you have accepted that your personal information will be handled in accordance with this Policy by accepting the Membership Agreement. Below is a summary of Bluetooth SIG, Inc.’s online privacy policy.  
>  
> 
> **Types and uses of account information.**
> 
> In order to execute the Membership Agreement, Your account information is used in the following ways:
> 
>   * **User IDs and Passwords.**
>
>> Provides you with access to your profile areas and to protected content.
> 
>   * **Account Information.**
>
>> These tell us more about who you are, who you work for, how to contact you, and your interests in receiving SIG information.
> 
>   * **Member Feedback and Support.**
>
>> Provides a mechanism for requesting information from Bluetooth SIG, Inc. Also used to tell us how we can improve our services and site designs.
> 
>   * **Email Correspondence.**
>
>> Used to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. Also used to distribute information about Bluetooth SIG, Inc., our specifications, and services.
> 
>   * **Transactions.**
>
>> Shows which products and services you have requested.
> 
> 

> 
> We will only use your personal information in the ways specified when it was collected or in the ways that are necessary for us to execute agreement with you. We will not subsequently change the way in which we use your personal information, unless you consent to the new usage.  
>  
> 
> **Security measures.**
> 
> We continually strive to protect the information you share with us. For example, if you make an UnPlugFest registration with us, we encrypt your credit card number. Access to your personal information is limited to people engaged by the Bluetooth SIG Inc. who need it to do their job.
> 
> For purposes above, authorized third party agents may also need access to some of your personal information. For example, if we need to ship something to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. We only provide third party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the by you requested service or transaction. We do not otherwise share your personal information with third parties, unless you have granted us permission to do so.  
>  
> 
> **Data Retention.**
> 
> Bluetooth SIG, Inc. will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.  
>  
> 
> **Linked web sites.**
> 
> We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites.  
>  
> 
> **Cookies.**
> 
> The Bluetooth SIG, Inc. Web site may use _cookies_. Cookies help us provide a better user experience by measuring which Web site areas are of greatest interest. Bluetooth SIG, Inc. also uses cookies when you register for one of our Web programs. In this situation, a cookie will store useful information that enables our Web site to remember you when you return. Bluetooth SIG, Inc.  can only read cookies from the member web site.
> 
> If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still access most of our Web sites. Some Web sites will not allow you to complete certain activities if cookies are disabled.
> 
> We may display advertisements from third parties. Third party ad-serving companies control which ads are shown. These ad-serving companies may use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information from you. Advertisers use this information to target the ads and measure their impact.  
>  
> 
> **Accessing and updating information.**
> 
> We need your help in making sure your business information is correct in our systems. Please notify us of changes to your name, company, title, phone number or email address.  
>  
> 
> **Unsubscribing.**
> 
> Each email newsletter has instructions on how to unsubscribe.  
>  
> 
> **Newsgroups / Forums.**
> 
> Bluetooth SIG, Inc. forums are open  to all SIG,Inc. members. Please consider this before posting.  
>  
> 
> **Transfer of personal information to the U.K.**
> 
> We may process or store your information in our U.K. databases.  
>  
> 
> **Policy updates:**
> 
> All updates to this policy will be posted here. Last update: September 01, 2001.  
>  
> 
> **Need help with an update, access, or unsubscribe request?**
> 
> Contact the Support Team at: **bluetooth@bluetooth.org**. To aid in processing your request, please include the following details:
> 
>   * Contact information (your name, address, email, etc.)
>   * Name of the program where you want the update applied
>   * Details of the request (e.g. change of email address, unsubscribe from a newsletter, review of my personal information, etc.)
> 

|
